(Episode 95) Before returning to the country,
I've already reported to the police
and handed over
all the evidence from two years ago
to them.
It's been a while,
so the police should be here soon.
Dad, you can't escape.
How dare you report me to the police and arrest me?
I'm your father!
Right in front of me,
you still want to hit my daughter?
Do you
want to go to jail
right now, huh?
Mom,
please sit down.
Dad,
there's something you might not know.
Since three months ago,
I've started
buying shares of the Curtis Group.
Now, my mom is the largest shareholder
of the Curtis Group.
It was my mom's
strong support
and investment
that allowed you to succeed in your business.
It's time for you
to leave the Curtis Group.
How is that possible?
Where did you get the money?
This card has no spending limit.
You can swipe it however you want.
You really don't need me
to acquire the Curtis Group
and transfer it to your name.
No need.
I will personally
take back the Curtis Group.
I will slowly pay back
the money I owe you.
I don't need you to repay me.
We should draw a clear line between public and
private life.
Although we are together now,
I hope that
we can rely on each other emotionally
and be financially independent.
You don't need to worry about it.
You
heartless daughter!
When I
pushed your mother down the stairs,
I should have strangled you to death.
Today, I'm going to
kill you both,
you evil women.
Stop!
Let go of me!
Are you okay?
Oliver Curtis,
someone reported you
for attempted murder.
Now come with us
and cooperate with the investigation.
Move.
You called the police to arrest me.
You heartless daughter, you will die miserably!